JANUS QUEK

PROGRAMMER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Singapore

PHONE

+65 81898717

EMAIL

janus.quek@digipen.edu

PLACE OF BIRTH

Singapore

NATIONALITY

Singaporean

LINKS

LinkedIn

SKILLS

C++

.

C#

• • • 0 0

Python

• • • 0 0

Unity

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Unreal Engine

• • • 0 0

Adobe Photoshop

• • 0 0 0

LANGUAGES

English

• • • • •

Chinese

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Japanese

• 0 0 0 0

PROFILE

A passionate back-end game engine developer from Digipen Institute of Technology Singapore.

Experienced in Engine Architecture (ECS), Audio Technology, C# Scripting Integration via Mono, Editor via IMGUI, Serialization via Rapidjson and binary, Memory Management, and gameplay via C# scripting.

Attained various academic achievements and project awards during my time in Digipen.

Currently on a scholarship with The Infocomm Media Development Authority of Singapore.

See more at: https://www.linkedin.com/in/janus-quek/

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Game Design, DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore

Singapore

Sep 2018 — Aug 2022

GPA: 3.71

Helped develop Howl: A Tale of Wolves in 2019:

Awarded 3rd Place for Claude Comair Grand Prize for Game of the Year

Awarded Best Sophomore Game

Awarded Best Sophomore Technology

Finalist for Best 2D Graphics Technology

Finalist for Most Innovative Design

Helped develop Spellthief in 2018:

Awarded Best Freshman Technology

Finalist for Best 2D Physics Technology

Finalist for Best Music and Sound Design

Finalist for Best Artificial Intelligence

Admitted into the Director's List for every semester so far

Game and Entertainment Technology, Temasek Polytechnic

Singapore

Apr 2013 — Mar 2016

Admitted into the Director's List for AY2013/2014 October semester

Has worked with Unity for game development projects.

Has been contracted by the school after graduation to continue working on a project as a paid contractor.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

National Serviceman, National Service

Singapore

Oct 2016 — Aug 2018

Programmer Intern, Bandai Namco Studios Singapore

Singapore

Oct 2015 — Mar 2016

Worked on a prototype of a new game idea in Unreal Engine 4

Worked with both Blueprints and C++ on Unreal Engine 4.

Worked with WPF in C# in developing a software.

Worked with MySQL to create a database to work in conjunction with said software.

REFERENCES

References available upon request